# Mustafa Dalğa Front End Developer

https://github.com/mustafadalga

https://medium.com/@mustafadalga

🕷 https://www.npmjs.com/~mustafadalga

in https://linkedin.com/in/mustafadalga/

https://stackoverflow.com/users/10636297/mustafa

M https://codepen.io/mustafadalga

#### Profile

I see software development as a hobby rather than a job.

I have had the opportunity to use many technologies by developing desktop and web applications for 5 years. I continue to learn and grow in life using research skills and accumulated experience, following a "be your own teacher" philosophy.

Javascript is my main programming language. I share the projects I have developed to learn and improve myself on Github as open source. I am working as a Front-end developer at Heybooster.

My vision is to develop myself as a high quality software developer/engineer following the ethical code of hackers.

# Professional Experience

**Heybooster,** Front End Developer

09/2020 - present Technologies: Pure Javascript, Vue JS, Vuex, Webpack, HTML5, SCSS(CSS3), Vite.js,

Typescript, Tailwind CSS

I had the following tasks in the app.heybooster.ai .

### Responsibilities

- √ Maintainable and sustainability of front end projects
- √ Creating a sustainable architecture
- √ Responsive Design

Responsive development of non-Responsive designs by rearranging or rewriting them

- √ Improving Web performance
- Improvements to improve site transitions and user experience in addition to increasing site speed
- Detecting and resolving bugs for front-end development
- √ Productivity Improvement
- √ Improving legacy code
- √ Correcting or rewriting codes according to clean code principles.
- √ Defining code writing principles to be used within the team to write code better and improve code readability and sharing them with the team
- √ Creating and using Vuex modules by actively using Vuex to keep data more organized. and easier to manage
- √ Testing all improvements/fixed bugs
- √ Upgrade Vue v2 to Vue v3: https://medium.com/heybooster/adventures-of-a-front-enddeveloper-migration-of-front-end-project-e3b949bdde90

#### Free Software and Open Source Developer, Software Developer 2

Technologies: Javascript, Vue.js, Javascript, Python , PHP , HTML5 , CSS3 , Bootstrap

Development of projects using various technologies

- Real Time Two Player Intelligence Game Tactix | React.js ☑
- Tooltip generator | React JS ☑
- Connect Four Realtime Intelligence Game | Vue.js ☑
- Quiz Application Vue.js ☑
- Forex Exchange □
- Music Player | Vue.js □
- Computer Lab Automation | Vue.js ☑

02/2019 - 10/2020

- Typing Game | Vue.js □
- Multi Level Memory Game | Vue.js ☑
- Multi Level Puzzle Game | Vue.js
- Breakout Game | Vue.js ☑
- Zou Farm Landing Page ☑
- Heybooster Landing Page ☑
- Foundation Landing Page 🛮
- Tour and Travel WebSite Landing Page ☑

#### Private Procare Health Services, Front End Developer

08/2017 - 02/2019

Technologies:Pure Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, PHP

Responsibilities

- √ Responsive Design
- √ Development of privateprocare.com 
  □
- √ Development of a platform for human resource management enprestis.com 

  □

#### Vizyon Dijital, Software Developer

04/2017 - 08/2017

Technologies:PHP, Pure Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS

Responsibilities

- √ Responsive Design
- √ Detecting and resolving bugs for front-end development
- √ Improving legacy code

#### Education

Marmara University, GPA:3.22 / 4 | | 84.7 / 100

2016 - 2020

CEIT(Computer Education and Instructional Technology)

İstanbul, Turkey

Cizre Technical High School, GPA = 3.76 /Top scoring student

2011 - 2015

Information Technologies - Top scoring student

Turkey

# Projects

#### Tactix | Real Time Two Player Intelligence Game 2

07/2022 - 08/2022

React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js, Socket.io, Redux Toolkit, TailwindCSS, Vite.js

#### Connection Four Realtime Intelligence Game,

Vue.js,Firebase,Materialize CSS,HTML5,CSS3 ☑

Tooltip Generator, React JS, Redux Toolkit , Tailwind CSS , HTML5 , CSS 🖸

Quiz Application, Vue.js , Typescript, Vite.js, SCSS, CSS3 🗷

Forex Exchange, Vue.js , Javascript, SCSS, Socket.io

Computer Lab Automation, Vue.js, Laravel, PostgreSQL, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap ☑

Music Player, Vue.js, Vuex, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5 2

Typing Game, Vue.js, CSS3 , HTML5 ≥

Multi Level Memory Game, Vue.js, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5 2

Multi Level Puzzle Game, Vue.js, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5 2

Breakout Game, Vue.js, Canvas, CSS3, HTML5 ☑

Zou - Farm Landing Page, JavaScript, SCSS - CSS3 , HTML5 🛭

Heybooster Landing Page, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ☑

Foundation Web Site UI Design, JavaScript, SCSS - CSS3, HTML5 🛭

# Skills

Vue.js | React.js | Javascript | Typescript | SCSS | CSS3 | Vuex | Webpack | Vite.js | Redux toolkit HTML5 | Jquery | Bootstrap , Materialize CSS, Tailwind CSS | Git

# Certificates

• Cambly Certificate of Accomplishment ☑

• Certificate of Completion | English Language ☑

# **References**

**Recommendations**, https://www.linkedin.com/in/mustafadalga/details/recommendations/

# Publications

**Techinal Blog Posts,** https://medium.com/@mustafadalga